http://www.locscientific.com/privacy-policy

ADA Compliance Hood
Variable Air Volume (VAV)
Lab Safety Cabinets
Ready to get started?
Get a Free, No Obligatory
Laboratory Design Today!
Laboratory Sinks
Ready to get started?
Get a Free, No Obligatory
Laboratory Design Today!
ADA Compliance Hood
Variable Air Volume (VAV)
Fume Hood FAQs
Ready to get started?
Get a Free, No Obligatory
Laboratory Design Today!
Electrical Outlets
Ready to get started?
Get a Free, No Obligatory
Laboratory Design Today!
"ELECTRIC WIRE HARNESS" Workbench
Ready to get started?
Get a Free, No Obligatory
Laboratory Design Today!
Medical Seating
Ready to get started?
Get a Free, No Obligatory
Laboratory Design Today!
Boil Out Curing Station
Ready to get started?
Get a Free, No Obligatory
Laboratory Design Today!
Evidence Bench
Ready to get started?
Get a Free, No Obligatory
Laboratory Design Today!
Spray Booth
Ready to get started?
Get a Free, No Obligatory
Laboratory Design Today!
3D Rendering Samples
Ready to get started?
Get a Free, No Obligatory
Laboratory Design Today!
Introduction
At LOC Scientific, Inc., we respect your privacy. We want to maintain your confidence in our handling of any data and information that is collected during your visit to our web site. We have developed and provided this Privacy Policy to inform you of our practices and policies regarding the collection, use, maintenance, and disclosure of your personal data and information.
We are committed to providing you with adequate information so you can make an informed decision whether to visit our web site and whether you wish to voluntarily provide any personal data or information, e.g., your name, e-mail address, telephone number, etc. Our Privacy Policy is described in the following sections.
Cookies
“Cookies” are small data files that are written to and stored on your hard drive when you visit a web site. They do not read files on your hard drive.
Like most web sites, we use cookies to personalize a user’s experience of our web site and to make it easier for users to complete forms. Our cookies do not track user movement once you leave our web site, except for noting your destination address.
Most web browsers allow the user to be notified upon the proposed installation of a cookie and the user can then decline the cookie. Even if you decline the cookie, you may continue to use our entire web site.
We use data and information received from our cookies for marketing purposes and to improve our on-line offering of services and products. We may also do so to evaluate our site’s technical capacity and to review the navigational structure of our site, e.g., to revise or restructure our web site for easier and more intuitive movement throughout.
Currently, the data and information we collect with cookies is only reviewed in an aggregated form, which is not personally identifiable. In the future, however, we may correlate the data and information received from cookies with personally identifiable information, to identify specific users and track their web site usage. This personally identifiable information will be limited to contact information, such as the user’s name, address, phone number, fax number, and e-mail address. Our use of this combined information will continue to be solely for the purposes stated above with respect to information collected through cookies.
Whether or not the data and information received from cookies is correlated to any specific user, we do not, and will not, disclose, sell, rent or share any data or information derived from cookies with any third parties other than to LOC Scientific Inc.’s affiliated companies (“Affiliates”), except for personally identifiable information saved in cookies when you register for or enroll in a program or service as we disclose in accordance with our policy for Voluntarily Provided Information set forth below, or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy.
Log Files
We also review data and information contained in log files located on our web server, which record the date and time of each visit to our web site, the user’s IP (internet protocol) address, the referring IP address or domain (the prior web site visited), and the files viewed on our web site (including HTML pages, graphics, etc.). We use log file information to analyze data in the aggregate to determine the trends and usage of our site. We can not correlate the log data to identify specific users.
We do not, and will not, disclose, sell, rent or share any information derived from log files with any third parties other than to Affiliates, or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy.
Voluntarily Provided Information
If you register for or enroll in a program or service through our web site, make purchases from our on-line offerings, respond to a request for information or make any other on-line request of us, you will be voluntarily providing personally identifiable information. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, we ask that you please do not provide the requested information. You may nevertheless continue to use most of our web site, subject, however, to the collection of information through cookies and log files as discussed above. If you have previously provided personally identifiable information by registration through our web site, you may request to be removed from our active database of mailing lists (see the discussion below).
Voluntarily provided information is used to send you announcements of new products, updates, and promotional information, as well as to provide the services or goods that you request and give you better customer service. We share personally identifiable information with our Affiliates, as well as with our third-party business partners, sales representatives and distributors (collectively, “Partners”) who may provide the requested goods or services to you directly or otherwise contact you directly. Moreover, we rely on various third-party service companies (“Service Companies”) to provide certain services (e.g., shipping, credit card billing) for which it is necessary to provide users’ personally identifiable information.
We do not, and will not, disclose, sell, rent or share any personally identifiable information received as a result of enrollment, registrations or e-commerce transactions on our web site with any third parties, other than our Affiliates, Partners, Service Companies, or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy.
Please note that although we may seek to require that Affiliates, Partners, and Service Companies use information regarding our users only in the ways permitted by this Privacy Policy, we do not control and are not responsible for their privacy practices, or those of any other party.
Collection of Data & Information by Our ISP
Our Internet Service Provider (ISP) also collects certain information about your visit. It is the same information contained in a log file that we collect and analyze, i.e., the date and time of the visit, the user’s IP (internet protocol) address, the referring IP address or domain, and the files viewed on our web site (including HTML pages, graphics, etc.). In addition, our ISP has access to back-up files containing the personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide (even if your input fails). The ISP does not disclose, share, release, publish, disseminate, rent, or sell any personally identifiable information to any third parties, but does use the log files to analyze data in an aggregate form, which is not personally identifiable information.
Links to Third-Party Web Sites
Through our web pages, you may connect to third parties’ web sites via hyperlinks, and the connections may or may not be obvious. We are not responsible for the collection, use, maintenance, sharing, or disclosure of data and information by such third parties. We encourage our users to be aware of the varied privacy policies of web sites that they visit.
Correspondence
We maintain and review e-mail correspondence that you send to us. We will use (and maintain in a file specific to you) the personally identifiable information disclosed in the e-mail. Because such correspondence contains information that is not transmitted through the operation of our web site, it is not subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Required Disclosures of Data & Information
In addition to disclosures to our Affiliates, Partners, and Service Companies, and regardless of anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we may disclose personally identifiable information, with or without prior notice to you, when we believe that the law requires it, in response to subpoenas or at the demand of governmental agencies, to protect our systems or business, to protect other visitors to the web site, or to respond to an emergency. If you partake, or we reasonably suspect you of partaking in any illegal activity we may also disclose your personally identifiable information, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order. We may also make disclosures of your personally identifiable information with your affirmative consent.
Maintenance & Transmission of Data & Information
Although we use reasonable efforts to maintain the privacy of your personally identifiable data and information, due to technological limitations, and the risk of unlawful interceptions and accessing of transmissions and/or data, we cannot completely assure you, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable data and information, and any other electronically communicated information, will be absolutely confidential.
For all e-commerce transactions, we use industry-standard commercial encryption technology to protect the data and information that you transmit to us via our web site. Although this technology is not flawless, we believe that it provides reasonable protection for your data and information. We will endeavor to update our protective devices as encryption technology develops further.
Once received, personally identifiable information is protected from outside LOC Scientific, Inc. by “firewalls,” and access within LOC Scientific, Inc. is generally limited to the sales, marketing, and information technology departments. We also seek to require our Affiliates, Partners and Service Companies to exercise reasonable efforts to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Your Right to Review & Modify Data & Information
You have the right, at any time, to review and/or modify any of your personally identifiable information that you provide during registration, or any other voluntarily provided information. You may also remove yourself from our active databases of e-mail lists. To do so, you should send an e-mail to info@dev.devurl.info requesting that (a) we provide a copy of your profile of personally identifiable information, (b) we update or modify certain personally identifiable information, or (c) you be removed from our databases of active e-mail lists. We will endeavor to comply with your request as soon as reasonably possible. To protect your confidentiality, we can only send a requested profile to the e-mail address listed in the profile. In any event, our back-up files will maintain copies of your personally identifiable information. We reserve the right to contact former customers or users of the web site from time to time.
Users Under 13
This web site is not directed at children under the age of 13. If you are younger than 13, please do not provide any personally identifiable information in connection with your use of the web site.
Assignment
We reserve the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from our visitors to a third party in the event that we sell or transfer substantially all of our assets related to the web site to such third party.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Due to changing technological and marketing demands, we must reserve the right to change our policies regarding the privacy of your personally identifiable information in the future. If that happens, we will endeavor to promptly update this Privacy Policy. We may also attempt to provide a message to our customers whose e-mail addresses we have, in conformity with this Privacy Policy, advising of any such change(s). Your continued use of the web site following changes to this policy will indicate that you accept the changes.
Conclusion
We hope that this Privacy Policy helps you to make an informed decision whether to visit our web site and/or to provide us with certain information.
If you have any questions, concerns or problems, we encourage you to email to info@dev.devurl.info. We greatly appreciate your suggestions on how we can improve our Privacy Policy or any aspects of our web site.
Let's Begin Your Project Today
Get Started
Copyright ©2020 LOC Scientific. All rights reserved
Privacy Policy | Sitemap
